A Guide to the Papers of William H. Kennon, 1808-1903
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 February 15 (Box 4)
- Lucy [Heth?] to Mrs. Nancy Selden ca.1881 March 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 March 30 (Box 4)
- Lucy [Heth?] to Mrs. Nancy Selden ca.1881 March 31 (Box 4)
- Lucy [Heth?] to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1881 April 6 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 April 16 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 April 19 (Box 4)
- J. J. Barclay to Mrs. Kennon 1881 April 21 (Box 4)
- The Flock Book 1881 April (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 May 17 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 May 21 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 June 28 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 June 30 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1881 Jan-June (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1881 July 9 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 July 12 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 August 25 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 September 3 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 September 13 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 September 14 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 September 28 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 October 1 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 October 10 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 November 17 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 December 14 (Box 4)
- Receipts 1881 July-December (Box 4)
- H. Heth to Mrs. Nancy Selden [?] ca. 1881? (Box 4)
- Lucy Heth to Mrs. Nancy Selden ca. 1881? (Box 4)
- [?] to Mrs. Nancy Selden ca. 1881? (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 Jan 5 (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Kennon 1882 Jan 12 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 Jan 12 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 Jan 24 (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Kennon 1882 Jan 30 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 February 13 (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Murry 1882 February 20 (Box 4)
- Chas. Selden to Charles R. Kennon 1882 February 23 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry ca.1882 February 24 (Box 4)
- C. R. Kennon to Charles Selden 1882 February 27 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 March 3 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 March 6 (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to C. R. Kennon 1882 March 6 (Box 4)
- Andrew Johnston to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1882 March 17 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 March 21 (Box 4)
- Chapter one of [?] 1882 March 29 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 March 30 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 April 11 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 April 17 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 May 1 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry ca.1882 May 6 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 June 16 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 June 26 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1882 Jan-June (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 July 4 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 July 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 July 24 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 September 11 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 October 14 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 October 26 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 October 30 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 November 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 November 27 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1882 December 14 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to Herman Stump (copy) ca. 1882? (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry (copy) ca. 1882? (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1882 July-December (Box 4)
- Contract for Mill 1883 Jan 9 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 Jan 8 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 February 6 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 February 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 March 13 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 March 16 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 March 19 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 April 9 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 April 13 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 April 23 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 May 1 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 May 4 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 May 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 May 17 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 June 7 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 June 19 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 June 23 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 June 27 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1883 Jan-June (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 July 12 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 July 20 (Box 4)
- Contract for ferry at "Norwood" 1883 August 7 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 August 13 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 August 22 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 September 6 (Box 4)
- W. S. Waring & Son to James Murry 1883 September 27 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to Herman Stump 1883 September 29 (Box 4)
- Herman Stump to W. W. Kennon 1883 October 2 (Box 4)
- T. J. Branch to William Upshur Kennon 1883 October 10 (Box 4)
- W. L. Waring to William Upshur Kennon 1883 October 15 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 October 16 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon [?] to Miles [?] 1883 October 22 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to Herman Stump 1883 October 24 (Box 4)
- W. L. Waring to W. U. Kennon 1883 October 23 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry ca. 1884 October (Box 4)
- W. Snydor to R. Gray 1883 November 8 (Box 4)
- Herman Stump to W. W. Kennon 1883 November 20 (Box 4)
- F. C. Leake, Jr. to William Upshur Kennon 1883 December 6 (Box 4)
- William Upshur Kennon to Herman Stump (copy) 1883 December 7 (Box 4)
- Herman Stump to William Upshur Kennon 1883 December 15 (Box 4)
- Herman Stump to William Upshur Kennon 1883 December 21 (Box 4)
- W. B. Montague to W. W. Kennon 1883 December 26 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1883 December 26 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1883 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Business Letters 1883 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Bills 1884 (Box 4)
- Business letters to Kennon, Gray & Co. 1887 (Box 4)
- Insurance Policy 1888 July 2 (Box 4)
- Business letters 1889 (Box 4)
- Diary of William Upshur Kennon ca.188[?] (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous 1890 (Box 4)
- Contract for ferry at "Norwood" 1891 April 21 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts and Business lettersunitdate 1891 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1893 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1898 (Box 4)
- Bank book of William Upshur Kennon 1897-1899 (Box 4)
- Contract between Hugh Nelson and Polly Nelson 1900 August 20 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts and Business letters of C. R. Kennon 1902 (Box 4)
- N. O. Clef to Chas. R. Kennon 1903 March 10 (Box 4)
- B. R. Selden to Charles R. Kennon 1903 June 1 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1903 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1905 (Box 4)
- Stock Certificate 1910 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous n. d. (Box 4)
- Farm Book, 1881-1883 (Box 4-A)
- Bank book of William Upshur Kennon 1899-1903 (Box 4-A)
- Journal, 1808 Beverley Randolph includes Negro [slave] records (Box 4-A)
- Ledgers
  - Farm Book, 1873-1875 of William Upshur Kennon; includes produce and stock used and sold (Othertype Ledger)
  - Smokehouse Book, 1881-1883 (Othertype Ledger)
  - Corn Book, 1883 C. R. Kennon (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1827-1828 of John Heth (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1822-1824 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1824-1825 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1825-1827 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1827-1828 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1827-1831 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Bank Book, 1828-1832 of Beverley Randolph (Othertype Ledger)
  - Time Book, 1873, 1876 (Othertype Ledger)
  - Time Book, 1882-1883 (Othertype Ledger)
  - Balance Book, 1887-1903, including balances, 1887-1888; goods purchased, 1889-1899; estate settlement of Mrs. S. A. Lawson 1903 (Othertype Ledger)
  - Farm Journal ,1840-1842 of W. A. Kennon (Othertype Ledger)